Contact

yadelskyiviktor@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/viktoryadelskyi (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

React.js

JavaScript

TypeScript

Languages

English (Professional Working) Ukrainian (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

React. Lite level

React JS. Practical Course 2020 (Hooks, Classes, Redux) JavaScript v.2.0

Viktor Yadelskyi

Software Engineer

Lviv, Lviv, Ukraine

Summary

I have master degree in computer science and more than three years of web development experience. I'm experienced in building and maintaining responsive websites. I possess proficient knowledge on main frontend technologies: JavaScript, React, React Hooks, Redux; Also I know how to work with: CSS preprocessors (SASS/ LESS), Bootstrap, FlexBox, Grid, Ajax, npm/yarn, webpack, and Git. For all of my works, I have maintained one common thing, i.e, cleanness. My code is always well structured so that any child can easily follow along with it. Finally, I try to think of the targeted audience and code accordingly by fully understanding the flow and logic.

Experience

EPAM Systems

2 years 2 months

Trainee Software Engineer

February 2023 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Lviv, Lviv, Ukraine

Student Software Engineer

January 2022 - February 2023 (1 year 2 months)

Lviv, Lviv, Ukraine

Фриланс

Frontend Engineer

July 2021 - October 2021 (4 months)

I took part in a short-term commercial project in the e-commerce domain. My responsibilities included creating markup and writing front-end logic by using React.

The team had 2 FE devs (including me) and 1 BE.

Main technologies used by me: TypeScript, React (with hooks), CSS preprocessor (SCSS), Webpack.

Education

Ternopil Ivan Puluj National Technical University Master's degree, Computer Science · (2019)

Ternopil State 'Ivan Pul'uj' Technical University Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2018)